{
  "Index": {
    "title": "Hello world!",
    "language": "en"
  },
  "Navbar": {
    "home": "Home",
    "quiz": "Quiz",
    "about": "About",
    "language": "Language"
  },
  "Home": {
    "quiz": "The Meuch Quiz",
    "title_1": "Explanation",
    "title_2": "Course",
    "text_1": "Welcome to our Climate Quiz! The aim of this quiz is to test your knowledge of climate change and its solutions, while demystifying certain preconceived ideas. We want to help you distinguish between false information and real climate solutions. Get ready to plunge into the world of climate with instructive and engaging questions. Each question will address a specific aspect of climate change, from greenhouse gas emissions to sustainable solutions.",
    "text_2": "You'll be asked a series of questions. You'll have to answer them by choosing the answer that seems most appropriate to you. At the end of the quiz, you'll be able to see your results. But be careful! Your choices have consequences and will have a positive or negative impact on the health of your planet.",
    "button": "Test yourself"
  },
  "About" : {
    "title": "About us",
    "text": "Welcome to The Meuch! We're a dynamic team of passionate Meuchers. Together, we form a tight-knit Meuch, working hard to spread Meuchitude and achieve our common goals. Join us in our Meuch adventure!"
  },
  "Quiz": [
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What would be the temperature of the Earth without an atmosphere?",
        "answers": [
            "+15Â°C",
            "0Â°C",
            "-50Â°C",
            "-18Â°C"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
        "information": "Fortunately, the natural phenomenon of the greenhouse effect retains some of the sun's heat in the atmosphere!"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which gas has the most powerful greenhouse effect?",
        "answers": [
            "CO2",
            "Water vapor",
            "Methane",
            "Argon"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
        "information": "Water vapor contributes 60% to the greenhouse effect. However, human emissions of this gas through industry have limited effects as the lifespan of water vapor is short."
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "In winter and in equal quantity, which of these foods emits the most CO2?",
        "answers": [
            "Martinique banana",
            "Spanish tomatoes",
            "Picard rutabaga",
            "Colombian coffee"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
        "information": "In equal quantity, producing a tomato in winter generates more CO2 today than transporting other foods..."
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which country has the highest greenhouse gas emissions per capita?",
        "answers": [
            "The United States",
            "Australia",
            "Norway",
            "Japan"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
        "information": "Surprising!"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "The production of energy is our main source of CO2 emissions. What is the second?",
        "answers": [
            "Deforestation",
            "Volcanic activity",
            "Cow flatulence",
            "Burning Man"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
        "information": "It is deforestation, which accounts for about 15% of our emissions today."
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "In terms of transportation, which action would have the most impact?",
        "answers": [
            "Launch a major plan to promote bike taxis",
            "Improve the efficiency of airplanes",
            "Build a global network of high-speed trains",
            "Develop telecommuting"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
        "information": "Air transport remains one of the major sources of the increase in our carbon footprint, according to the project."
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "If all the energy I consumed was of human origin, how many humans would I need in my service?",
        "answers": [
            "2",
            "20",
            "200",
            "2000"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
        "information": "This is the argument taken up by many advocates of degrowth!"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "In terms of food, which solution is the most effective?",
        "answers": [
            "Eat less meat",
            "Install 'clean' cooking stoves in developing countries",
            "Implement a more efficient and sustainable rice cultivation",
            "Stop eating red tuna"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
        "information": "Eating less meat would be the most effective solution according to scientists from the project."
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Which action would reduce our greenhouse gas emissions the most?",
        "answers": [
            "Grow our vegetables",
            "Stop deforestation",
            "Remove gasoline vehicles",
            "Close carbon-emitting power plants"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
        "information": "To be taken on a global scale (obviously ðŸ˜€)"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which action would allow me to reduce my carbon footprint the most?",
        "answers": [
            "Lower the heating setpoint by 1Â°C",
            "Postpone the purchase of a new smartphone by a year",
            "Consume one meatless meal per week",
            "Turn off lights when leaving a room"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
        "information": "But feel free to follow the other suggestions, it can't hurt..."
    }
]
}

